(Howard:)He was just wondering
if he wore skintight jeans and a tank top...
(Howard:)...if he'd get his shrimp lo mein for free.
(Penny:)What are you saying?
That I'm using my body to get dinner?
That I'm some sort of
Chinese food prostitute?
(Howard:)Yeah, Raj, what are you saying?
(Penny:)Let me tell you something,
I pay my own way in this world.
(Penny:)I don't rely on anybody.
- What was that about?
- He has a nervous bladder...
(Howard:)...when he's stressed out.
(Howard:)Kind of like a puppy.
Here, Leonard. Ten, 11, uh, 12... $14.
It's 14.50, but it's okay.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good. Dinner's here.
(Penny:)Yes, dinner's here.
And I'm having takeout food.
(Penny:)- Okay.
- You're damn right it's okay.
I've been having leftovers for four days and
I wanted something different. So sue me.
(Sheldon:)Forgive me, Penny, but that would be
the very definition of a frivolous lawsuit.